Magic the Gathering just
sold the exact same
cards at two different
prices in one drop
Same product different price
tags no explanation Hey
ninjas Wizards of the
Coast dropped their latest
secret lair with identical
card sets priced differently
The community is absolutely
losing it over what
feels like blatant price
manipulation but here's what's
really wild Every other
TCG at least pretends
there's value justification for
price differences different art
foiling packaging Magic just
said nah pay more
because we said so
They literally said the
quiet part out loud
about arbitrary pricing My
hot take This is
wizards testing how much
disrespect their player base
will tolerate before jumping
ship What's your breaking
point with Magic Drop
it below I read
everything