Magic the Gathering just
sold the exact same
cards at two different
prices in one drop
Same product different price
tags no explanation What's
up fellow ninjas In
this video I'm going
to give a quick
update on the latest
Secret Lair controversy from
Wizards of the Coast
Their latest Secret Lair
drop had identical products
at different price points
The community is absolutely
losing it over what
feels like blatant price
manipulation But here's what's
really wild Every other
trading card game at
least pretends there's value
justification for price differences
Different art foiling packaging
Wizards of the Coast
just said nah pay
more because we said
so They literally said
the quiet part out
loud about arbitrary pricing
My hot take This
is Wizards testing how
much disrespect their player
base will tolerate before
jumping ship What's your
breaking point with Magic
the Gathering Drop a
comment below to let
me know I'll see
you guys in the
next video