Magic: The Gathering just sold
the exact same cards at
two different prices in one
drop. Same product. Different price
tags. No explanation. Hey Ninjas!
Wizards of the Coast dropped
their latest Secret Lair with
identical card sets priced differently.
The community is absolutely losing
it over what feels like
blatant price manipulation. But here's
the part that's really wild—
Every other TCG at least
pretends there's value justification for
price differences. Different art, foiling,
packaging. Magic just said "nah,
pay more because we said
so." They literally said the
quiet part out loud about
arbitrary pricing. Hot take: This
is Wizards testing how much
disrespect their playerbase will tolerate
before jumping ship. What's YOUR
breaking point with Magic? Drop
it below, I read everything.