Hey Ninjas! WhatsApp just dropped
a bombshell that could change
AI chatbots forever. They're introducing
per-message charges for AI bot
developers operating in Italy. Every
single message your AI chatbot
sends will cost money. This
isn't just about Italy though.
WhatsApp is testing the waters
before rolling this out globally.
For businesses relying on AI
customer service, costs could skyrocket
overnight. Small developers might get
priced out completely while big
tech gets even more dominant.
This could either kill innovation
or force developers to build
smarter, more efficient bots. Either
way, the free AI chatbot
party is officially over. Drop
a comment — what do
you think?