Magic The Gathering just
sold the exact same
cards at two different
prices in one drop
Same product Different price
tags No explanation Hey
ninjas Wizards of the
Coast dropped their latest
secret lair with identical
card sets priced differently
The community is absolutely
losing it over what
feels like blatant price
manipulation But here's the
part that's really wild
Every other TCG at
least pretends there's value
justification for price differences
Different art Foiling Packaging
Magic just said nah
pay more because we
said so They literally
said the quiet part
out loud about arbitrary
pricing My hot take
This is Wizards testing
how much disrespect their
player base will tolerate
before jumping ship What's
your breaking point with
Magic Drop it below
I read everything